30 years ago,
I found the book of the dead.
Now because I read from the book...
Misartar.
Evil has found me.
All roads to destroying this evil
lead to wear it all began.
The cabin.
- Let's go back there and end it all.
- You know I'm down.
The sooner this book
is six feet under, the better.
Yeah!
Here's the plan.
- Whoa!
- Shoot first, think never.
Whoa!
That didn't work.
Present the book to me
and we'll finally end this.
Ta demuche.
Pablo!
You have no idea what you're doing.
Of course I know what I'm doing.
I wrote this book.
Your stupid mortal toys
mean nothing to me.
Take the deal
then go back to Jacksonville.
I am offering you
the undo button you wanted.
Normal life in Jacksonville,
the three of us.
- I can do that.
- Truce.
Yeah!
Whooo!
Jacksonville here we come.
Mamma!
Atar. Artha.
Artica abomino!
I have fought with Atilla the Hun
and Genghis Khan,
And this dipshit is my only hope?
Oh, fuck. What a mess.
Summu Nura.
Ashrica.
Akrem.
Ash...
Jacksonville, I love you!
We love you, Ash!
I know you do!
Hey, I love me too!
Ash! Ash! Ash!
Oh, Jefe.
You know. You don't have to call
him that any more Pablo.
'Cause now he's just "water trash,"
like everyone else in this town.
Especially non tippers like you, buddy.
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, come on, Kell,
Ash did what he had to do.
He saved us.
And left Ruby in charge.
You know what, I don't trust that bitch
as far as I can throw her.
Kelly, there's someone wanting to pay.
Pull!
Looking good, Eli.
Hey, Sailor.
I had fun last night.
I think I remember that.
This is my daughter, Hannah.
Oh, how nice for you to meet me.
Can I, um, touch it?
My God.
How does it work?
Uh, well, I think it's pretty obvious.
Ladies, I'm gonna be honest with ya,
I'm not drunk enough to know if
this is good-weird or bad-weird.
But I'll get there though.
Fu..
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
My God...
I left the windows down in the Delta.
Whoa!
Hey, hey! Time out!
You're not supposed to be here.
Didn't you get the memo?
- There's a truce!
- Talk to Ruby.
She sent us!
Balls to the wall!
Your truce is over, Ashy Slashy!
What'd you call me?
Ashy Slashy, hatchet and saw
Takes your head and skins you raw
Ashy Slashy, heaven and hell
Cuts out your tongue
so you can't yell...
What the fuck is that?!
Shoot it in the head!
Nooo!
Jefe!
Your blade!
Ugh.
Huh?
Oh!
Give me your eyes!
Don't you want to fuck me now?!
Huh.
Get her off me!
I think we're good, Kell!
Fucking skank!
You will die like all the others!
One by one, we will take you!
All of you!
Ladies first.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Well, I guess it's safe to say,
the truce is over.
Told you Ruby couldn't be trusted.
We've got to put our little
thinking caps on
and do something...
Yes! You know I'm in.
I have been waiting to kick her ass.
Yeah, amen to that.
But how, Ruby could be anywhere?
I know where she is...
Ruby is in Elk Grove, Michigan.
That's my hometown.
Okay, that's a very specific guess.
The Deadite gave it away with that song.
That damn song...
Alright.
We're gonna go to Elk Grove.
We're gonna find Ruby
and I'm going to bury
that Kandarian Dagger
deep into her strangely beautiful neck
and kill her where she stands.
We'll be back in Jacksonville by Friday.
Pablo, first round
of 'Ritas is on you, because...
Oh, because it's the drink of my people.
That's a little racist, don't you think?
Well, yeah.
Sinkholes are still being reported.
And look at this, Kenward County.
Violent crime and murder up 200%
from this time last year.
Yeah, Ruby's evil is seeping everywhere.
Alright. We need a sketch of her
to show the people in town.
- Pablo?
- I'm on it.
So, uh, why so long since
you've been home?
Oh, who drank all the beer?
I got it.
Um, you.
Your bladder must be ready to explode.
Oh, please,
I've been whizzing the whole time.
Ugh!
_
Do it! I dare you.
- You do it.
- Chicken.
- Don't say that.
- Run!
Ashy Slashy's coming to get you!
You think Ruby's here?!
In a crack house?
No, this is my house.
Or at least it used to be.
Oh, it's, it's...
nice.
Your parents still live here?
My parents died a long time ago.
Just um, give me a sec.
I've never seen
the Jefe like this before.
Whatever happened in this town
seems to really haunt him.
Look at this creepy fucker.
Where?
He was right...
dude, he was right there.
Oh, shit!
Asshole.
Oh!
You come here to rob me, punk?
Think I won't fight back?
I'm not robbing you.
Ashley?
Hello Dad.
Been a long time.
You look...
Old.
- Bloated. Like a sack of...
- Yeah, I get the idea.
How you been, pop?
- What do you want?
- Nothing.
Can't a guy come and see his own father?
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's um, a utility hand.
A friend made it for me.
Check it out. I'm better, stronger...
- Faster?
- Yeah!
Bullshit. Looks like some
piece of crap made in China.
What was that gun shot?!
Alright, put down the guns!
- What is going on?
- You got a green card kid?
Kelly, Pablo, meet my father.
Whoa. Filthy and fine.
Brock Williams.
But you can call me Cock.
He's your father alright.
Um, I thought you said
your Dad was dead.
Dead? He's the one that died. Not me.
Uh, we were sort of dead to each other.
What have you done now?
Nothing. We're just looking for someone.
Pablo...
I drew most of it while
the car was moving, but...
What? You're looking for Bigfoot?
It was a bumpy ride!
Okay, you know what? Forget it.
You don't want to help, that's fine.
Some things never change.
Oh, still the victim with you, huh.
Always somebody else's fault.
Somebody else made you go to that cabin.
Somebody else chopped your hand off...
- Ah, no, I did that.
- Somebody else killed your girl.
No, I did that too.
Come on, Dad, you know
exactly what happened.
Why didn't you set
those people straight?
Because you should have.
Instead you let 'em beat you down
and you ran away with
your tail between your legs.
Thank God your mother
wasn't here to see that.
I did what I had to do.
Ashley, it's taken me a long time
to get my life back together.
I think it's best that you and
the "illegal" here just leave.
Kelly, would you like
to have dinner with me?
That's a hard pass.
Get out.
Let's go.
Elk Grove.
Hasn't changed a bit.
What's the plan?
We split up. Ask around.
You!
You ruined my life.
I've ruined a lot of people's lives.
Here, man. I've got some change.
_
How... what the...
How did...
Thanks.
Okay, let's go.
Jacksonville's waiting.
Whoa, Ash Williams.
Ash?
Ash Williams, is that you?
Linda Bates!
Holy hell... Wow.
It's been so long.
You look great in that waitress get-up.
Probably even better out of it.
Same Ash.
All okay here?
Yeah.
Little Tommy Emery?!
It's Sheriff Emery now.
And I'm all grown up.
You can ask around.
Oh.
Oh, you...
- No! You married Safety Boy?
- Who?
That's what we called him
back when he was a Hall Monitor.
Remember the time you peed your pants
outside the locker room?
Because you were leaning on the door.
- Guilty.
- Hey, that was such a long time ago.
- Right, honey?
- No.
Can you give us a second?
Sure.
Mm, mm, mm...
Hey.
Hey!
You've got some huge balls
showing your face in this town.
Yeah, I do.
Notice I never wear gym shorts.
I'm here on business,
looking for a woman.
She's bad news.
If I don't find her,
you might actually have
something to do around here.
Well then, let's find her for you.
Everyone, this is Ash.
Some of you may know him as Ashy Slashy,
because he went crazy
and chopped up his friends.
Okay, that's not true.
I did not go crazy.
I knew exactly what I was doing
when I chopped up my friends.
And now, Ashy Slashy is back in town
looking for a new woman.
So, what do people think?
Should we help Ash find another victim?
Or should we kick him back
to whatever rock he was hiding under?
Fuck this sicko! He's got to go!
Yeah! Get him out!
Ashy Slashy!
Ashy Slashy! Ashy Slashy!
Ashy Slashy! Ashy Slashy! Ashy Slashy!
Ashy Slashy!
No.
No more running away.
Alright. Get the gum out
of your ears and listen up,
you inbred, degenerate screw heads...
except you Linda.
You're so not like them.
Yes, I am Ashy Slashy,
the Boomstick Butcher
with the Chainsaw Hand.
But you nimrods got me all wrong...
I'm here to save this town,
to save my town,
whether you like it or not.
Now I'm here looking for somebody.
Check it out.
She goes by the name of Ruby.
Anybody?
You use your chainsaw to draw that?
Time to leave, Ash.
Oh, I'm gonna leave alright.
And don't you worry,
after I save all your sorry asses,
you won't see me again
for another thirty years dicksticks!
- Loser!
- Yeah!
Ugh!
Nooooo!
Hey! Hey!
Take it easy.
Pablo?
What's wrong?
I just saw Ruby.
- Saw Ruby? Where?
- I don't know.
I just had a weird vision of her
in front of a big brick building.
There were uh, these
smoke stacks there...
Two big smoke stacks?
Yeah.
That sounds like the crematorium...
This is it.
I saw it so clearly.
Pablo, how long you
been having these visions?
Ever since Ruby put that book on my face
I've been having... nightmares.
But they happen while I'm awake.
How come you never said something?
I was afraid.
I don't know what's
happening to me, Jefe.
Lets go get some answers.
We gave peace a chance.
Now it's time for war.
Alright, you two go that way.
But remember, these weapons
are only gonna stun Ruby.
So use them to
knock her down or whatever.
Then before she heals...
I'm gonna put an end to this
horse pucky once and for all.
Oh, god!
Ruby!
I know you're out there!
Hey!
Creepy kid?
You grew up quick!
You should not have come back, Ashley.
Ugh.
Ash!?
- Ash?
- It's that way.
- Ah!
- Kelly!
Kelly!
Kell!
Yeah, that's it!
Run home and cry to Mamma!
You tell her Ashley J Williams
is looking for her.
Huh!
Oh...
Why you...
My goodness.
Kelly, you're stronger than Ash.
Why follow when you should lead.
Ah!
Join us.
♪ We're gonna get you... ♪
- Ah!
- ♪ We're gonna get you... ♪
Get this!
Hah!
Yippee Kai-aye mother fu...
Oh, shit...
Oh!
Fuck!
Help!
Ash!
Ash.
Ash?
You actually found me.
Don't be so surprised you know.
I do have my moments like this one.
- Hey.
- You broke our truce, why?
I had no option.
I had to summon you...
What? So you can sic your
creepy ass kids on me?
No.
My children have turned on me.
I have lost control of them.
They want the Necronomicon.
They're trying to destroy me.
Poor Ruby.
Yeah, welcome to my world, sweet cheeks.
Doesn't feel so good, does it?
At least you still have
all your appendages!
Now Ash...
I need your help...
Oh.
Oh, you need my help?
Okay, first of all,
screw you and your ugly ass kids.
Here's what, I need.
I need to be back in Jacksonville
on my second keg of beer,
putting my spicy man meat into
a mother-daughter sandwich,
that's what I need.
As unappetizing as that sounds,
you can still have all of that.
Just trust me.
Help me stop my childre...
Hey!
I wasn't done with her!
Help!
Pablo help!
Mamma.
Three creepy kids.
Well, Ruby's a big girl.
I'm sure she can handle herself.
Gah!
Where is the Necronomicon?
What have you done with it?
I'll never tell you.
Oh, those damn radar eyes.
Do I save her 'cause I should?
Or cause she's hot?
Mamma.
Alright, you naked assholes,
time to pick on someone your own size.
You want some?!
You feel that? Huh? Do you?
You feel that?
Do you?
The Necronomicon says you
are humanity's true savior.
This is where your story ends, Jefe!
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, creepy kid.
Playtime's over.
Night-night.
I told you you could trust me.
- Jefe!?
- Stay the fuck away from him!
I got this.
I've made a huge mess.
Yeah, you really fudged
the bowl this time, didn't you?
And now you want me to put
the old rubber gloves on
and help you scrub it clean.
Part of me is already
regretting calling you here.
Get used to that feeling.
- Where's the book?
- Hid it.
Go get it.
My children are too
powerful for me alone.
Ash, I need you.
All of you, help me retrieve the Book
and send them back to Hell.
Give me a second.
You guys good with that?
Huh?
Okay.
We get the Book.
Send your loser kids back to Hell...
we're back in Jacksonville by Friday.
Pablo, first round of 'Ritas
is on you, because...
Ah, yeah, you already used that one.
- Really?
- Word-for-word.
Wow.
Maybe I'm getting
that bad memory disease.
- Alzheimer's?
- Alzheimer's?!
That's a bad memory disease.
Why would you mention that?
Focus up, we got work to do!
Let's go save the world.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com